<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Academic</title>
    <link>https://bsouhaib.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://bsouhaib.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://bsouhaib.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://bsouhaib.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bsouhaib.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bsouhaib.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Souhaib Ben Taieb is an Associate Professor in Computer Science at University of Mons (UMONS) in Belgium. He is also an Adjunct Senior Lecturer in the Department of Econometrics and Business Statistics at Monash University in Melbourne, Australia. His research interests include statistical machine learning, artificial intelligence, time series analysis, probabilistic forecasting, temporal point processes, big data processing and smart grid analytics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From 2016 to 2018, Souhaib was a Lecturer in the Department of Econometrics and Business Statistics at Monash University in Melbourne, Australia. In 2015, he was a postdoctoral research fellow in the Spatio-Temporal and Data Science Group at KAUST. He was a visiting scholar at several international institutions, including the School of Earth, Energy and Environmental Sciences, Stanford University, and the Said Business School, University of Oxford. He received an M.Sc and a Ph.D. in Computer Science with a specialization in Machine learning from the Free University of Brussels in Belgium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Ben Taieb has received multiple awards including an Early-Career Faculty Research grant from Monash Business School, the Solvay Awards 2015 for his PhD thesis, an IEEE Power &amp;amp; Energy Society Award for the Global Energy Forecasting Competition 2012, and a Doctoral research fellow grant from the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research (FNRS).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
